xjtlu.edu.cn 2019-12-08

# Privacy | Xi'an Jiaotong-Liverpool University (XJTLU)

Please read these Conditions of Use carefully. They apply to the website you were using which linked to these Conditions of Use (the “Site”). They govern your use of the Site and of all other Xi'an Jiaotong-Liverpool University websites. 

Access to and use of the Site is provided by Xi'an Jiaotong-Liverpool University on the following terms. By using the Site you are acknowledging that you have read and accepted these Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy. 

We may change these Conditions of Use from time to time by updating this page. You should review this page regularly. Your continued use of the Site after changes have been made will be taken to indicate that you have read and accepted those changes. You should not use the Site if you are not happy with any changes to these Conditions of Use. You agree to use the Site only in accordance with these Terms and Conditions of Use for lawful purposes, and in a way that does not infringe the rights of, restrict or inhibit anyone else’s use and enjoyment of the Site. 

Prohibited behaviour includes (this list is not exhaustive) harassing or causing distress or inconvenience to any person, transmitting obscene or offensive content or disrupting the normal flow of dialogue within the Site and impersonating another person. 

##  1\. Disclaimer

Every effort is made to ensure the accuracy and currency of the information contained in pages of the Xi'an Jiaotong-Liverpool University Site and all subdomains thereof. However, contents are subject to change from time to time and the University can accept no liability for the accuracy of all the information presented at any given time. 

The University reserves the right to make changes without notice. Some links may lead to information maintained by third parties and the University accepts no responsibility for the accuracy or any other aspect of information obtained through such links. Every effort is made to ensure downloadable content is free from viruses. The University can accept no liability for damages resulting from virus infection. 

###  1.1. Study Programmes and Research Opportunities

Information on the University Site relating to taught study programmes and research opportunities is provided as advance publicity and for guidance purposes only. It does not constitute a contract. 

Every possible effort is made to ensure that information on study and research opportunities is accurate and current. However, this information is subject to change without notice both before and after a candidate's admission. Candidates are, therefore, advised to contact the relevant department before applying in order to confirm all details of what is currently available. 

##  2\. Copyright

All aspects of the Xi'an Jiaotong-Liverpool University Site - design, text, graphics, applications, software, underlying source code and all other aspects - are copyright Xi'an Jiaotong-Liverpool University and its affiliates or content and technology providers. 

In accessing the University web pages, you agree that any downloading of content is for personal, non-commercial reference only. No part of this Site may be reproduced or transmitted in any form or by any means, electronic, mechanical, photocopying, recording or otherwise, without prior permission of the University. 

For rights clearance please [contact us](https://www.xjtlu.edu.cn/en/contact). 

###  2.1. Trademarks and Logos

The University has registered as trademarks the words: 

Xi'an Jiaotong-Liverpool University, XiJiaPu and XiPu. 

The University trademarks and logo may only be used in applications approved by the University, e.g. in official documents. They may not be used in any other context without the express consent of the University. Requests to use the University logo should be made by contacting us. 

##  3\. Personal Privacy

Xi'an Jiaotong-Liverpool University recognises the importance of personal privacy. This document explains how we collect and treat personal information on the Web. 

###  3.1. What information is collected, and how is it used?

The University web servers automatically collect standard, anonymous information, like the IP address of your computer, the browser software used, the operating system, access times, pages visited. This information is used in an anonymous form to monitor usage and to assess the effectiveness of the University Site. 

In some sections of the University Site anonymous data such as browser type or IP address may be used to customise web page content. This information is used in an anonymous form to ensure appropriate and effective delivery of content. 

If you provide your email address by using subscription facilities or sending feedback, enquiries or requests by email, the personal information you provide (including your email address) will be used only to respond to your message or deliver the requested service. 

On occasion you may be asked to provide some limited personal information (such as name, postal address, email address), when requesting publications, information or services via the University Site. 

When providing this information, you may also be asked whether you wish to receive any further communication from Xi'an Jiaotong-Liverpool University thought relevant to you. 

Any personal information you provide will be used only for the reason specified at the point of collection. We will not sell, licence or trade your personal details to any third party. 

###  3.2. Cookies

In common with many other websites, we, or our suppliers/partners, may use standard technology called 'cookies' on this Site. Cookies are small files that are passed to your computer by the web server via your browser. Most standard web browsers may be configured to refuse cookies. 

Cookies are used to collect information to help us record how you navigate this Site and may be used to deliver services you have requested or to occasionally prepare customised pages. 

Xi'an Jiaotong-Liverpool University Site sets cookies including, but not limited to, the following. 

####  Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to help analyse use of our website. This analytical tool uses cookies to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information in an anonymous form. 

The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Site (including your IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is used to compile statistical reports on Site activity for the University in order to evaluate visitors' use of the Site. 

We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the Site in order to increase its efficiency. We collect this information in a way which does not identify anyone and we do not make any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our Site. To opt out of Google Analytics across all websites visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

Cookie Names:  
_utma  
_utmb  
_utmc 

####  Hobsons

The Xi'an Jiaotong-Liverpool University has a relationship with Hobsons Plc (Hobsons) and the web pages at [jlu.hobsonsradius.com](http://jlu.hobsonsradius.com/) are hosted by Hobsons as part of this relationship. [You can read a list of the Cookies used by Hobsons for the processing of information on these pages](http://www.hobsons.com/europe/cookies.php). 

More information on cookies, including how to control and delete them, can be obtained from [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). Please be aware that restricting cookies may impact on the functionality of our Site. 

####  DoubleClick Floodlight

We use DoubleClick Floodlight technology on some of our pages.  
The technology helps us to evaluate the success of our advertising campaigns on domains external to xjtlu.edu.cn by recording every time a user returns to the given page. No personally identifying information is ever collected. 

For more information about how to opt out of these cookies please visit <https://www.google.com/ads/preferences>. [Read more information about DoubleClick Floodlight](https://support.google.com/dfa/partner/answer/186739?hl=en). 

Cookie name  
• ad.doubleclick.net 

##  4\. Security

Appropriate security measures are in place to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of information collected from you, including measures to prevent, as far as possible, access to University databases by parties other than Xi'an Jiaotong-Liverpool University. 

##  5\. Contacts and Feedback

Any comments or feedback regarding this statement should be emailed to [webteam@xjtlu.edu.cn](mailto:webteam@xjtlu.edu.cn) or sent by post to: Web Development Manager, University Marketing and Communications Office, Central Building, Xi'an Jiaotong-Liverpool University, 111 Ren’ai Road, Suzhou Dushu Lake Science and Education Innovation District, Suzhou Industrial Park, Suzhou, P. R. China, 215123.
